honey.is 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Honey

Last updated: May 15, 2017

Front & Main, Inc. d/b/a Honey (“Honey”) has established a comprehensive privacy program, designed to help us respect and protect your data privacy rights. This Privacy Policy explains what information may be collected by Honey, how such information may be used or shared with others, how we safeguard it and how you may control its use. Honey wants you to feel safe, so please read this Privacy Policy carefully, because by using Honey you are acknowledging that you understand and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### Privacy Statement

Honey respects your privacy, as a result, we have developed this Privacy Policy. In order to optimize our products and services, Honey collects certain information provided by you, such as user name, email address, avatar and other information you provide when registering for an account, or on your user profile, as well as all content that’s been posted to Honey, whether through our site, via email or from other applications, including content such as text, links to other sites, files or images. (“Your Information”) We will use Your Information to respond to requests you may make of us, and from time to time, we may refer to Your Information to better understand your needs and how we can improve products and services. We will handle your Personal Information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Any other information transferred by you in connection with your use of Honey (“Other Information” - that is, information that cannot be used to identify you) may be included in databases owned and maintained by Honey or its agents. Honey retains all rights to these databases and the information contained in them. Other Information we collect may include your IP Address and other information gathered through our cookies.

### Protecting Your Information

Honey uses commercially reasonable and industry standard security measures to protect Your Information. We also use up to 256-bit SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption to transmit sensitive information. However, no internet transmission or storage of information can be completely ensured to be safe from intrusion. As such, Honey can’t guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us.

### Using Your Information

Honey uses the information it collects in order to provide you with the most efficient service and optimized user experience.

We may share Your Information with agents, contractors or partners of Honey in connection with services that these individuals or entities perform for, or with, Honey. Specifically, Honey uses vendors providing tools for analytics, customer support and general operations in order to better serve your needs and operate our business efficiently.

Honey reserves the right to share Your Information to respond to duly authorized information requests of governmental authorities or where required by law.

We may also provide Your Information to a third party in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of Honey to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat Your Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Honey does not sell, rent or lease any of Your Information to any third party.

### Opting Out

You can always direct us not to share Your Information with non-essential third parties, or not to send you newsletters, emails, or other communications by emailing us at [hello@honey.is](mailto:hello@honey.is).

You may opt-out of third party cookies from Google Analytics by visiting <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> and following opt-out instructions. We do not currently recognize or respond to browser-initiated Do Not Track signals as there is no consistent industry standard for compliance.

### Cookies

Honey uses a technology called a “cookie”. A cookie is a piece of information that we send to your computer or other device when you use Honey. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the site and help us analyze site usage more accurately. You can always disable cookies through your browser, but some of our features may not function properly if you do so.

### Anonymized Data

Honey collects and aggregates anonymized data (data that has been stripped of any user identifiable information) and metrics about overall usage. This may include pages you visit, the time of access, the device, browser or OS that you used and various other metrics necessary in order to maintain and improve user experience. This data is used by Honey in order to optimize user experience and to develop new products.

### External Services

In connection with your use of Honey you may sync your account with other services, such as social networks, or other applications which integrate with Honey. If you elect to sync to such services, Your Information will be disclosed and subject to the privacy policy of any such other services.

### Other Sites

Honey may contain links to other sites or services that we don’t own or operate. We don’t recommend and aren’t responsible for these sites or their privacy policies and practices. Be aware that these other services may set their own cookies, independently collect data or solicit personal information. You should assess the authenticity of any site which appears or claims to be part of Honey, and contact us if you have any questions or doubts.

### Reviewing your Information

You can access Your Information at any time in order to ensure its accuracy or make any updates as you may require through the use of “My Account” or by emailing us at [hello@honey.is](mailto:hello@honey.is).

### Changes

Honey reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy from time to time, as may be necessary in order to accommodate our business and our users. We encourage you to bookmark and review this Privacy Policy form occasionally in order to ensure that you are up to date on any changes. This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 15, 2017.

### Contact

If you have any questions, comments, suggestions or concerns, please feel free to email us at [hello@honey.is](mailto:hello@honey.is) at any time.
